<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Writeups on Personnal security blog</title>
    <link>https://thibaudrobin.github.io/writeups/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Writeups on Personnal security blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://thibaudrobin.github.io/writeups/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>ZedCorp Challenge - My name is Rookie</title>
      <link>https://thibaudrobin.github.io/writeups/hacklab-esgi-2019/zedcorp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thibaudrobin.github.io/writeups/hacklab-esgi-2019/zedcorp/</guid>
      <description>The ZedCorp challenge alias &amp;ldquo;My name is Rookie&amp;rdquo; was a realistic challenge proposed at Hacklab ESGI CTF 2019. ZedCorp is a small startup who work in computer science and particulary in development. The goal was to recover confidential files owned by the CEO.
For this challenge, I wanted to teach challengers the principle of SSH tunneling and basics of penetration testing.
Writeups wrote by others challengers (too many writeups you are mad &amp;lt;3) :</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Netrunner</title>
      <link>https://thibaudrobin.github.io/writeups/santhacklaus-2018/netrunner/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thibaudrobin.github.io/writeups/santhacklaus-2018/netrunner/</guid>
      <description>Netrunner is the second biggest challenge of the Santhacklaus 2018 CTF. The challenge is not really hard, but could be particulary annoying if you don&amp;rsquo;t know what to do. You need to have some skills in pentest web and medium skills in Linux system.
The challenge is divided in 3 steps. Each step has its own validation password (flag). So let&amp;rsquo;s begin with the first step !
1st step - You have a mission !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ArchDrive</title>
      <link>https://thibaudrobin.github.io/writeups/santhacklaus-2018/archdrive/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thibaudrobin.github.io/writeups/santhacklaus-2018/archdrive/</guid>
      <description>ArchDrive is the biggest challenge of the Santhacklaus 2018 CTF and my favorite one. It&amp;rsquo;s divided in 5 steps of increasing difficulty. The challenge is not really hard, but particularly long and time-consuming. You need to have some strong skills in web pentesting, some basic skills in forensic and medium skills in Linux system.
So, as you can see, the 5 steps have their own validation password (flag). Let&amp;rsquo;s start the challenge !</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>